这样不是很好么?
Isn't this nice?
我有点...想休息了
I kind of... prefer breathing.
加油  你做得不错
Come on, you're doing great.
你知道  运动是会上瘾的
You know, exercise is addictive.
喔...我能...
Wow...I can...
我知道为什么了
I can see why.
我想我需要减肥
Guess I need to drop a few pounds.
别对自己太严厉
Don't be so hard on yourself.
这不是马上能完成的事
It's not going to happen overnight.
有些人的新陈代谢是有点慢
Some people's metabolisms are just a little slower.
不是因为新陈代谢
It's not my metabolism.
我病了
I'm sick.
什么?
What?
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没什么
Never mind.
Hurley
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
好吧
Okay.
但是...这不是什么好事情
But...it's bad.
当我们刚坠机时
When we first crashed here,
我想这也不是太坏
I thought this isn't all bad.
我可以吃芒果减肥
It's like the all-mango diet.
我并没有刻意去这么做
I wasn't turning any heads or nothing,
但我确实是瘦了几圈
but I did drop a couple belt sizes.
然后我们找到了这个舱子
Then we found this hatch,
里面全是食物...
and it was full of food...
大堆的食物
tons of food.
我想把它们都扔掉  但是...
I tried giving it all away, but...
我还是留了点给我自己
I guess I kinda kept some of it for myself.
我希望我能把它们处理掉
Wish I could just get rid of it.
那就处理掉它们
Then get rid of it.
你想改变自我么?
You want to change?
那就改变吧
Then change.
感觉怎样?
How do you feel?
我感到自由了
Oh! I feel free.
有人找到了些东西
They found something.
快来
Come on!
快点  伙计们
Hurry, guys.
意大利饭  不错
Risotto. Nice.
不
No.
这些是哪儿来的?
Where did this come from?
Locke说他被门关在舱子里了
Locke said doors trapped him in the hatch.
也许就是因为这个
Maybe it was because of this,
就没人能看到这些是谁扔下的了
so no one would see who dropped it.
有谁昨晚看见过飞机了?
Any of you guys see a plane last night?
我看见了
Yeah, I saw it, Tattoo.
刚刚还想不说的
I just decided not to tell.
-还给我 伙计 拜托  -伙计  是我先看到的
-Hey, put that back, man. Come on.  -Oh, man, I saw it first.
你看到时我已经把它放我盒子里了
You saw me take those.You saw me put those in my box.
-不  把我的东西还我  -别冲动
-No. Gimme my stuff!  -Hold on, take it easy!
你们就像蝗虫一样  我们讲点次序怎样?
You're like locusts. How about a little order?
我们干吗不找个值得信任的人来看管这些呢?
Shouldn't we let someone trustworthy do this?
比如说你 婴儿绑票犯是么?
Like you, babynapper?
不  比如说Hurley  Hurley可以
No. Like Hurley. Why not Hurley?
他以前作过  现在可以再作
He's　done it before, he could do it again.
不  想也别想
No! No way!
我不要  不  我不干了
Not me! No! Not again! No.
嘿  嘿  伙计们 伙计们
OK, hey, hey, guys, guys.
要不不要找人管了吧?
How about no one's in charge, OK?
我确定大家都能做到只拿需要的那部分的
I'm sure everyone can manage to just take what they need.
好建议
Great plan, Moonbeam.
在那之后我们就能唱着歌来玩信任游戏了
After that, we can sing Kumbaya and do trust falls.
-放那里    -放这里
-put them in there.   -pull this over here.
这样太粗鲁了
...savages about it.
我们怎么样都可以
We can do it any way you want.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
别挡路
Out of my way.
你在干吗?
What you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
你在这儿找谁?
Who were you looking for up there?
没找谁
No one.
你好像在找什么人
it sort of seemed　like you were looking for someone.
-我在找你...   -我有点...
-I tried to find you...  -I kind a...
不想谈这个
don't wanna talk about it.
噢  好的
Sure. OK.
很奇怪  不是么?
Pretty weird, huh?
你说这个岛不想让你减肥...
You said the island won't let you lose weight,
你毁了你的储备  然后...
you destroy your stash, then bang...
天上掉下了更多的食物
More food falls from the sky.
那又怎样
How about that?
我很为你自豪
I'm proud of you.
为什么?
Proud of me for what?
没有兴奋异常
Not freaking out.
减肥成果怎样  Hugo?
How's the diet coming, Hugo?
很不错
It's OK.
我中午吃了沙拉和鸡胸
I had a salad and some chicken breast for lunch.
很好
That's great.
我保证会越来越容易的
It gets easier. I promise.
我听说你去看你妈妈了?
So, I heard you had a visit with your mom.
怎么样了?
How did that go?
很不错
It was good.
你不生她气了吧?
You're not still mad at her, then?
不了  我知道她带我来这儿是有原因的
Nah.　I know she put me in here for a reason.
什么原因?
What reason was that?
意外事故
The accident.
你今天想谈谈这个么?
You wanna talk about that today?
一定要说么?
Do we have to?
Hugo  你在这儿快两个月了
Hugo, you've been in here almost two months now.
差不多可以做点不情愿做的事了吧?
Don't you think it's time to start getting our hands dirty? Hm?
好吧  我们来谈谈...
OK, why don't we talk about
我给你布置的家庭作业吧?
the little homework assignment that I gave you?
家庭作业我从来都做不好
I was never really good at homework.
你记得你应该做什么吗?
Remember what you were supposed to do?
把你喜欢做的事列一张表
Just make a list of things that you like about yourself?
没人这么做过
Nobody else did it.
没人?  指谁?
Nobody else? Meaning?
Dave没这么做过
Well, Dave didn't do it.
他说这么做很蠢
He said it was a stupid idea.
你知道  我不是Dave的医生
Well, you know, I'm not Dave's doctor,
但我们谈过了他对你的影响是消极的
but we have talked about how he can be a very negative influence.
Dave是这儿最正常的人了
Dave's the most normal person in this place, man.
但他不想你改变  不是么?
But he doesn't want you to change, does he?
快  把球给我
Come on, give me the ball.
把球给我
Give me the ball!
伙计  伙计
Dude! Dude
我没人防守  这儿  这儿
I'm open! Dude! Dude!
把球给我
Give me the ball!
这叫运球
It's called "dribbling" not "drooling!"
叫运球
"Dribbling!"
投篮  快
Well, shoot it, then!
投篮
Shoot it!
什么...哦  好高的命中率
What? High percentage shot.
不错的选择
Excellent choice.
-投篮!    -你想一起来么  伙计?  来吧
-Shoot!    -Want in the game? Go for it.
我想他们不会介意的
Something tells me no one'll care.
你怎么了?
What's the matter with you?
没什么
Nothing.
伙计  伙计  别摇了
Dude! Dude, give up the rock!
好极了  把球传给场外的人
Fantastic. Give it to the guy who's not even in the game!
嘿  伙计  该吃墨西哥卷了
Hey, it's Taco Night, dude.
别管什么规矩了
Let's blow this pop stand.
怎么了?
What?
Brooks说...
Brooks said you're,
你对我影响不好
like, negative.
是么
Well, duh!
那么你是不想和我做朋友了?
So, what, you don't wanna hang out with me any more?
不  我不知道  只是...
No, I don't know, it's...
你这么相信那个骗子么  伙计?
That quack getting inside your head?
别听他的
Do not let him.
你还要考虑更重要的事
You got much more important things to think about.
是什么?
Like what?
就像吃软贝还是硬贝
Like, hard or soft shell, baby?
鸡肉还是虾肉
Chicken or shrimp?
酸乳酪还是热沙司
Sour cream or hot sauce?
恩  我想我能吃
Yeah, I guess I could eat.
是啊  我也这么想
Yeah, I thought so.
吃墨西哥卷去吧  朋友
Noche de Tacos, amigo.
很好  动动另一只看?
Good. Now, can you do the other one?
没X光  我只能尽力猜了
Without an X-ray, you'll have to do with my best guess.
抱歉
Sorry.
能撑住么?
How you holding up?
就看Jack怎么猜了
Depends on Jack's best guess.
有点小骨折
There's a small fracture,
很微小的一点
probably hairline.
这样就能在我给你固定前减退肿大了
This will reduce the swelling until I get a splint.
我要多久才能走?
How long until I can walk on it?
你得躺上几个星期
Keep off it a couple of weeks.
在营地那儿有个轮椅...
There's a wheelchair back at camp...
不要
No.
我不需要轮椅
I don't need a wheelchair.
我们走回海滩时在机身上弄了两块板
We took a pair of crutches from the fuselage when we moved down the beach.
好的
OK.
马上回来
I'll be back in a while.
他可以逃走的
He could've escaped.
什么?
Sorry?
Henry
在门落下的时候
During the lockdown.
我受伤了
I was hurt
他可以逃走的...
He could have escaped...
但是他...他回来帮我了
But he came back to help me.
他为什么那么做?
Why would he do that?
他不是回来帮你的  John
He didn't come back to help you, John
他回来是他认为他的故事完美无瑕
He came back because he thought his story was gonna check out.
他已经死了
He was dead already.
四个月前
Four months ago,
我是救援队中的一个
I was part of the search party.
Henry Gale摔在热气球外面  脖子断了
Henry Gale was hanging out of the basket, neck broken.
就是说你看到他时他已经死了
So he was already dead?
是的
Yes.
然后你埋了他  做了个墓碑
And then you buried him and left the grave marker?
是的
Yes.
你那么做前应该仔细看看他的皮夹
You really should have checked his wallet before you did that
我觉得Henry Gale没纸来写自己的想法
I assume Henry Gale did not have any paper on which to compose his thoughts,
所以他得临时找纸
so he had to improvise.
能写的地方不多
There wasn't much space for that.
Jennifer...
你是对的
Well, you were right.
横跨太平洋不是一件容易的事
Crossing the　Pacific isn't easy.
我欠你一瓶啤酒
I owe you a beer.
我要徒步去找海滩  在那儿生火求援
I'm hiking to one of the beaches to start a signal fire,
但是如果你看到了这段话  那表示我没有成功
but if you're reading this,I guess I didn't make it.
我很抱歉  我爱你  Jenny
I'm sorry. I love you, Jenny.
永远爱你
Always have, always will.
你的Henry
Yours, Henry.
那么告诉我...
So tell me...
Henry Gale断了脖子还能给他妻子写东西么?
how did Henry Gale write a note to his wife with a broken neck?
不是我
It wasn't me.
不是我杀的
I didn't kill him.
你不明白...
You don't understand...
你怎么知道他妻子的名字? 你拷问过他?
How did you know his wife's name?  Did you interrogate him?
拜托  听我说
Please...just listen...
-拜托  我只是一个...  -你们有多少人?
-Please  I'm just a...  -How many of you are there?
如果我和你说了  我会被他整得很惨的
If I tell you about them, you have no idea what he'll do.
他?
He?
你是说他们的头儿?
You mean their leader.
有胡子的那个?
The guy with the beard.
他?  没有他
Him? He's no one.
没这个人
Nothing!
你们的人在哪儿?
Where are your people?
-我不能...   -你们有多少人?
-I can't...   -How many of you are there?
-你不明白    -你要明白
-You don't understand!    -Understand this!
只给你三秒钟时间
Hey.You have three seconds to answer my question.
你们有多少人?
How many of you are there?
-1  -他会杀了我
-One.  -He'll kill me!
我会杀了你
I'll kill you.
-2  -Sayid
-Two.  -Sayid!
你不能这么做
You can't do this!
我不是个坏人
I am not a bad person!
你到底怎么了?
What the hell's wrong with you?
怎么了?  我听到枪声
What's going on? I heard a shot!
怎么了?
What happened?
他是个骗子
He's a liar.
没事  带他离开这儿
It's fine. Just get him out of here.
Jack
Jack?
Jack!
我处理好了  John
I've got it covered, John.
谢谢
Thank you.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我看见你在做东西
I noticed you were building something.
我想你用得着这个
I thought maybe you could use this, for whatever it is.
你很关心人  Charlie
That's very thoughtful of you, Charlie
帮忙一起干吧?
Why don't you help me?
你在做什么?
What are you making?
抓住那头
Hold that end.
做咖啡馆么?
Is it a Starbucks?
帮我扛下那些木头
Help me carry one of those logs, please.
你不说么?
Are you gonna tell me?
还不是时候
Not right now.
你不在这的
You're not here!
等等
Wait!
等等  Dave
Wait! Dave!
没事吧  Hurley?
You OK, Hurley?
你们有看见一个人从这跑出来么?
Did either of you see a guy run through here?
穿着浴衣的人
In a bathrobe?
手上拿着一个椰子
With a coconut?
没有
No.
只看见一只北极熊拿着芒果站在滚筒上
I saw a polar bear on rollerblades with a mango.
我什么也没看到
I did not see anything either.
恩  我也没有
Yeah, me neither.
4  18  15
-哦  伙计     -16 23 42
-Aw, dude.     -16, 23, 42
好卑鄙  Leonard
Pretty sneaky, Leonard.
你在用你的那些数字装疯卖傻是么  伙计?
Using those magic numbers of yours as a psych-out, aren't you, man?
哦  对了  你在装聋作哑
Oh, yeah, that's right. You just play dumb.
我对你的念叨很感兴趣  伙计
I'm onto your juju, man.
那些只是数字  伙计
They're just numbers, dude.
那是什么?
What the hell is that?
我的下午点心
It's my mid-afternoon snack.
伙计  是芹菜  芹菜可不是点心
Dude, that's celery. Celery is not a snack.
Leonard有饼干  你能拿一块
Leonard's got graham crackers. You should snag one.
他不会发现的
He won't notice.
他能怎么做  叫你"23"?
What's he gonna do? Call you a "23"?
4 8 15 16
4 8 15 16 Hike!
15  16  23  42...
Hugo  你的药
Hey, Hugo. Here's your meds.
谢谢  Lazenby护士
Thank you, Nurse Lazenby.
伙计  你想和我一起离开这儿么?
Dude, you wanna get outta here with me?
别吃这些镇定剂
Don't take the horse tranquilizer.
你说什么  离开这儿?
What do you mean, "get outta here?"
我是说逃走  伙计
I mean, escape, man.
我和你  越快越好
Me and you. ASAP.
他们看你看得很紧  伙计  我们得分头行动
They're getting to you, dude. We gotta split.
-Brooks医生说...  -Brooks医生不在乎你  伙计
-Dr.Brooks says...  -Dr.Brooks does not care about you, man.
他就是那个给你药的人
He's the one prescribing that crap.
这到底是什么药?
What the hell is it anyway?
科隆纳泽潘
Clonazepam.
Hugo? 药有问题么?
Hugo? Something wrong with your meds, there?
不  呃...我和Dave在...
Me and Dave were just, you know...
谈些事情
talking about stuff.
好的  很抱歉打扰了
Right. Well, sorry to interrupt.
你好  Dave
Hello there, Dave.
你好  Brooks医生
Hello there, Dr. Brooks.
今天感觉怎样?
And how are you today?
非常好
Never been saner.
我要拍几张照片放在公告板上
I'm taking pictures for the bulletin board.
就只有你们两个没拍了
I've got everyone except you two.
你们不介意吧?
Would you guys mind?
好的
OK.
你们可以靠近一点
Why don't you get a little closer together?
要我们装出很高兴的表情么?
Are you gonna make us look at the ducky, too?
说"茄子"
Say cheese!
-"茄子"     -"茄子"
-Cheese!    -Queso!
很好
Great.
那么你吃药要水么?
OK, you...you need a little water with that?
不用  我可以
Nope. I'm good.
那好
OK. Well, fine.
回头见  伙计们
See you later, guys.
谢谢你们的合作
Thanks for the photo op.
伙计...
Dude...
伙计
Dude
革命已经开始了  伙计
The revolution has begun, man.
时机合适的时候  我们就走
Lay low. When the time is right, we fly.
(巧克力奶油饼)
你得用扭的...
You gotta twist it.
才能弄到奶油  硬拉只会得不偿失
To get the frosting. Pulling it'll only break your cookie.
我知道了不能一开始就成为行家
Well, that's what I get for not going to the expert in the first place.
有事么?
What can I do you for, Deep Dish?
呃...我要点东西
I was kind of looking for something.
算了吧  买卖结束了
Forget it. I'm done trading.
我的东西足够开一家连锁超市了
I got enough food now to open a chain of mini-marts.
嘿  你想Sayid需要一份工作么?
Hey, you think Sayid needs a job?
事实上...
Well, actually,
我希望你帮个忙
I was sort of hoping you'd do me a favor.
希望你还记得我帮你找过树蛙...
Remember when I helped you out with that tree frog...
被你捏死的那只
which you killed?
是的  我记着
Yeah, I remember.
我有点...
Well, I sorta...
想要一些药
need some medicine.
你要什么?
What do you need?
一种叫科隆纳泽潘的药
It's called Clonazepam.
什么?
Clonaze-what?
那是什么?
What the hell's that?
吃了药后就能...
It's so you can calm down
不看...看不见...
or for when you're seeing things...
那些...不应该存在的东西
that aren't supposed to be there.
你看见什么了?
What stuff are you seeing?
我不知道...
I don't know,
可能是个穿浴衣的秃子
maybe, like, a bald guy in a bathrobe.
你是说那个人?
You mean like that guy there?
上当了
Gotcha.
你真可笑  你在做什么
Think you're funny. What are you doing?
你以为你是谁?
Who do you think you are?
放开我
Get off!
Let go of me!
死猪头
Lambchop!
巨型  怪物
Babar! Jabba!
再说?
Stay-Puft!
猪油  猩猩  傻子
Lardo! Kong! Deep dish!
把他拉开
Get him off me!
放开我
Let go of me!
Hurley
放开我
Get off me!
你到底出什么毛病了?
What the hell's the matter with you?
你这个疯子
You're crazy!
我不是疯子
I'm not crazy.
他打了你了  是么?
So he just attacked you, huh?
说话注意点  小妞
Try to contain yourself, Freckles.
什么?  我是在担心你
What? I'm worried.
你看起来是像被人踢了屁股
You look like you got your ass kicked
为什么你不开始一段冒险呢?
Don't you got an adventure to get to?
我想Timmy在那条路上掉到井里了
I think Timmy fell down a well over that way.
认真点  他怎么...
Seriously, though, why'd he...
我不知道
I got no idea!
我什么都没做
I didn't do nothing.
他就一下冲过来
He just Hulked out on me.
毫无原因
For no reason at all?
好吧
OK.
你可以走了  祝你好运
You walk off and have yourself a nice long giggle.
走路当心点
But steer clear.
那人是个疯子
The man is crazy.
Hurley?
你没事吧?
You OK?
你和Sawyer怎么了?
What happened with Sawyer?
我不想谈这事
I don't wanna talk about it.
那么...
So,
你打了他?
you beat him up?
我想你知道发生什么了
Guess you know what happened, then
我是站在你这边的 不管你说什么...
I'm on your side. Whatever you...
听着  我不想谈这个  好么?
Look, I don't wanna talk, OK?
怎么?
What?
这花生酱够多的了
That's a lot of peanut butter.
我要带上足够的蛋白质
I'll need a lot of protein where I'm going.
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
回去山洞那儿
Back to the caves.
那儿已经没人住了  我就不会打扰大家了
No one lives there,  so I won't bother anybody.
知道么  我要单独住  变成他们中的一个
I'm gonna live alone and be one of those guys.
那些疯了的人
You know, the crazy guys,
有胡子没衣服的那些
with a big beard, no clothes,
还裸着身子向人扔泥巴
who's naked and throws doody at people.
Hurley  你不需要这么做的
Hurley, you don't have to do this.
让我单独呆着
Just leave me alone.
你帮不了我
You can't help me
没人可以
No one can.
你不在这的
You're not here.
你是在医院里的
You were in the hospital.
你不可能在这的
You can't be here.
抱歉  伙计
Sorry, dude.
我就在这
I am here.
我喜欢和我妈妈和睦相处
I like that I have a good relationship with my mom.
我喜欢我的爷爷Tito永远开心
I like making my Grandpa Tito laugh.
我喜欢鸡肉
I like chicken.
不  最后一个不是指你的  Hugo
No, that last one wasn't about you, Hugo.
鸡肉那个?
I like that I like chicken?
那么告诉我...
So tell me,
写那些时感觉怎样?  很难是么?
how did it feel writing that? Was that difficult?
有点  我想有些词我拼错了
Kinda. I think I messed up some spelling.
我发现你没说你的长相
You didn't say anything about the way you look.
你...
Are you
对你的长相满意么?
comfortable with your appearance?
这不像...
Well, it's not like...
我是说  这不是我能改变的
I mean, I can't really do anything about it, right?
如果我...
If I...
不是这么胖...
wasn't so fat...
他们就不会死了
they never would have died.
那块板上站了23个人
There were 23 people on that deck.
它的承载量是8个...
It was built to hold eight.
不管你上不上去它都会塌的
And it would have collapsed whether you went out there or not.
是的  但我就是走上去了
Yeah, but I did walk out there.
它确实就塌了
And it did collapse.
是我杀了他们
And I killed them.
那是个意外
It was an accident.
是我的错
It was my fault.
但是在那些人死后
Look, after those people died
你呈现出紧张的状态
you were in a practically catatonic state.
你不说话
You stopped talking,
你不出门...
you stopped going out,
甚至不睡觉
you stopped sleeping.
但你从没停止过吃
But you never stopped eating,
因为这样你才能惩罚你自己
because that's how you punish yourself.
Dave说你是对的
Dave's right about you.
你是个骗子
You're nothing but a quack.
Dave不想你减肥  是么?
Dave doesn't want you to lose weight
你知道  Dave很关心我
You know, Dave cares about me.
他是我的朋友
He's my friend.
好吧
well,
我给你看样东西
I'm gonna show you something,
这会使你伤心
and it may upset you.
就是这张照片
This is the photo
我为了公告板拍的
that I took for the bulletin board.
Dave不是你的朋友  Hugo
Dave isn't your friend, Hugo...
因为Dave根本不存在
because Dave doesn't exist.
醒醒  伙计
Psst! Hey! Wake up, dude.
终于你可以睡得这么熟了  伙计
Finally. You could sleep through a damn NASCAR race, man.
伙计  你不是...你是...你是个幻觉
But, you're not... You're...You're a hallucination.
-噢  -那是个幻觉么?
-Ow!  -Was that a hallucination?
也许我想象你在打我
Maybe I just imagined you slapped me.
噢  混蛋
Ow! Damn it!
我能整晚打你
We can do this all night.
Brooks医生给我看了那张照片
Dr. Brooks showed me a picture from the rec room,
我胳膊搂着的  是空气
and my arm was around nothingness.
呃  用软件改过的吧?
Uh... Kinko's? Photoshop?
你真的以为他们把彗星给炸了?
Think they really blew up the Death Star?
不
No
那么就别乱说了  来吧  我们要赶时间
Then stop talking crazy, man. Come on, we're on a clock here.
嘿  你要不要走了  伙计?
Hey, you in or you out, dude?
好了  来吧来吧
OK, come on, come on.
你看看  Marcus的面条没吃完
Yo, check it out, Marcus didn't finish his lasagna.
这真浪费
That is a waste, man.
路上吃?
One for the road?
等等
Wait for it
等等...
Wait.
踮脚走  当心点
Tippytoes, big guy
好了  伙计  你有钥匙吧
OK, man, you got the keys, hombre.
你早些时候从Brooks桌上拿的
You took 'em off Brooks' desk earlier.
快点伙计  打开它
Come on, man, open it, open it.
你能感受到么?
Oh-oh-oh! Can you taste that?
自由的味道
That is freedom, baby.
你知道什么味道比自由更好么?
Know what tastes even better than freedom?
乳酪三明治
Cheeseburgers.
来吧  伙计
Come on, man!
一起吃东西去
Chili fries on me.
我不能这么做
I don't think I can do this.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉?
Sorry?
什么  你在开玩笑么?
What, are you kidding me?
你不是真的
You're not real.
你帮我逃走帮我拿奶酪三明治是因为...
You're trying to get me to run away and get cheeseburgers because...
我想要三明治
I want cheeseburgers.
你吃了那些药了么  伙计?
Did you take those pills, man?
没有  我只是不想走
No, man, I'm just not coming.
听着  你不想我好  你不想我转变
Look, you don't want me to get better, you don't want me to change.
你不需要转变  伙计
You don't need to change, man
你很好  你很棒
You are fine. You are great.
不 我不好
No, I'm not.
你想让我永远这么胖
You just want me to stay fat.
你不想我好
You don't want me to get better.
你不在乎我吃到死
You wouldn't care if I ate myself to death.
别这么干  伙计
Do not do this, man.
如果你现在不和我走
If you don't come with me right now,
你永远
you will never
也走不了了
get outta here.
再见  Dave
Bye, Dave.
你发现我的拖鞋  意外么?
You wouldn't happen to have my slipper, would you?
谢谢
Thank you.
噢  伙计
Oh, man!
你把花生酱倒在上面了
You got peanut butter on it.
好了  听着...
OK, look,
我知道你现在有点想不通
I know you're freaking out right now,
我非常非常抱歉  但是...
and I'm sorry, but...
这是黎明前的黑暗
it's gonna get a little worse before it gets better.
黑暗?
Worse?
是的...
Yeah.
有点
Kinda.
你准备好了么  伙计?
You ready, dude?
你记得那晚你看着我关上窗么?
You remember that night you closed that window on me?
你记得你之后干了什么吗?
Remember what you did after that night?
是的
Yeah.
我了解到你是虚构的
I realized you were imaginary.
而且...
And...
那是个转折点
that was a breakthrough.
过了不久
And a little while later,
Brooks让我出来了
Brooks let me out,
我回家和我妈住在一起
and I went home to live with my mom,
我在Cluck那儿找了份工作
and I got my job at Mr. Cluck's back,
然后我好了起来
and I got better.
好的  很好  非常好
OK. Good. Great. Yeah.
除了...
Except,
我和你说...呃...
see, here's the thing. Uh...
那些事都没发生过
None of that ever happened.
什么?
What?
你还在圣罗萨  伙计
You're still at Santa Rosa, man.
你没离开过医院
You never left the hospital.
那是...
That's...
-不可能的     -我知道这很难接受
-That's not possible.     -It's hard, I know.
但是  我是说  全部这些
But, I mean, all this?
你  我
You? Me?
这个岛
This island?
花生酱...这全是假的
That peanut butter? None of it's real, man.
一切都没发生过
None of it's happening.
全是你想出来的  伙计
It's all in your head, my friend.
在你关上那窗子之后  你的脑子就被套上了枷锁
The second you closed that window, your brain popped a gasket.
你又重新昏迷了
You went back into your coma thing,
也就是此时此刻的你
and that's where you are right this very second.
在爱达荷州
In your own private Idaho
在圣罗萨医院
inside Santa Rosa.
不
No.
我有...
I had...
我妈妈...
My mom...
我的朋友Johnny...
My friend Johnny...
我赢了六合彩
I won the lottery.
真不错  伙计
Awesome, dude.
你用什么号码赢的?
What numbers did you play?
Leonard'的数字  是么?
Leonard's numbers, right?
从医院里听来的?  多么凑巧啊  你...
From the hospital? What a coincidence.
还在哪儿看到这些数字了?
You seen them around anywhere else?
-舱门上     -答对了
-The hatch.     -Bingo!
舱门上
The hatch.
你每隔108分钟就得按按键
With the button that you gotta push every 108 minutes
不然就是世界末日了
or the world ends.
噢噢噢  而且...
Oh, oh, oh, and
你要按哪些数字?
what's the code for the button?
噢  对了
Oh, yeah.
那些数字
The numbers.
但是我好多了
But I got better.
变了?
Changed?
你在说笑么?  看看你自己
Are you kidding? Take a look at yourself.
你在这个荒芜的岛上呆了两个多月了
You've been on a deserted island for over two months
你连10磅都没减下来
and you haven't dropped ten pounds.
这可能么  伙计?
How is that even possible, man?
我刚刚毁了我的储藏
I just destroyed my stash.
我一直在锻炼  Libby说那不是马上能完成的事
And I've been exercising. Libby says it won't...
对了对了  Libby
Right, Libby.
那个魔法般从岛的另一边出现的美丽金发小妞
The mega-cute blonde chick who magically appeared from the other side of the island.
噢  对
Oh, yeah,
她恰巧这么性感...
and who just happens to have the hots
就为了你
for you?
来吧  伙计  我们走走
Come on, man. Let's take a walk.
那么这些都是我想出来的?
So this is all in my brain?
每块石头  每棵树
Every rock. Every tree.
每只树蛙
Every tree frog.
甚至是我
Even me.
真的我  那个他们告诉你是虚构的...
The real me, the one they told you was imaginary?
他已经跳出窗外了  伙计
He went out that window, man.
现在他大概在一堆辣妹之间享受呢
Right now, he's probably bouncing from hot chick to hot chick.
你不同  你是真的
Unlike me, who's really you,
你有很重要的事要做
who's got more important things to do.
那么你是我想出来的
So I'm making you up?
可以这么说
Well, sorta.
我是你潜意识的一部分  伙计
I'm part of your subconscious, man.
这个岛上的所有人都是
All the people on this island are.
你是我哪一部分?
What part of me are you?
我是你想醒来的那部分  伙计
I'm the part of you that wants to wake up, man.
跟我来
Follow me.
就这了  伙计
This is it, dude.
这?
It?
终结的地方
The big finale.
你所有问题的答案
The answer to all your problems.
使你醒来的一个方法
A way for you to wake up,
从这里摆脱出去
snap out of it.
我不想自杀
I don't wanna kill myself.
谁说了是自杀了  伙计?
Who said anything about killing yourself, man?
这会使你回到你的生活
This is gonna bring you back to life.
你离开这里的唯一方法
The only way for you to bust out
就是告诉你自己
is to tell your mind
你不相信这的一切
that you don't believe any of this.
那么...
So...
如果我...
if I...
这些全都结束了?
All this will be gone?
我会醒来?
I'll just wake up?
是的
That's right.
当你醒来的时候
And when you do wake up,
来找我吧
come find me.
我肯定我想死你了
I'm sure I miss you.
在另一个世界见吧  Hurley
See you in another life, Hurley.
Dave
Jack还没回来么?
Jack not back yet?
没有
Nope
他会和海滩上每个人说我们抓了他们中的一个
He's telling everyone at the beach that we've got one of 'em.
我想大家会有很多问题要问我们这位房客的
Something tells me people have a lot of questions about our houseguest.
我想和他谈谈
I want to talk to him.
我想这不在今天的日程之上
I don't think that's on today's program.
尊敬的Ana Lucia 我不在乎你是怎么想的
Well, all due respect, Ana Lucia, but I don't care what you think.
就5分钟
Five minutes.
我就和他说5分钟
I earned five minutes with him.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
你的真名
Your real name.
你为什么不...
Why don't you
继续叫我Henry?
just keep calling me Henry?
我已经习惯这么叫了
I've gotten used to it.
你是故意被抓的么?
Did you get caught on purpose?
你和你们的人在这儿
You and your people have been here
呆了多久 只有上帝知道 然后你被一只网抓了...
for God knows how long, and you got caught in a net...
上帝不知道
God doesn't know.
什么?
Excuse me?
上帝不知道我们在这儿呆了多久了  John
God doesn't know how long we've been here, John.
他像世界其他地方的人一样也看不到这个岛
He can't see this island any betterthan the rest of the world can.
我能问个问题么?
May I ask you a question?
我可以经历这一切...
What possible reason could I have
到底是因为什么?
for putting myself through all this?
也许
Maybe
你们的人正在找这里
your people were looking for this place.
这里?
This place?
这个地方
This place
是个笑话  John
is a joke, John.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我爬过你们的通风口
I crawled through your vents
站在你们的电脑前
and I stood at your computer
你们的警报响了
as the alarm beeped.
你知道发生了什么吗?
And you know what happened?
计时器一直走到零
The timer went all the way down to zero.
然后一些有趣的红色图片就蹦了出来
And then some funny red pictures flipped up in its place.
就像象形文字
They looked like hieroglyphics,
但是
but
我不是个专家
I'm no expert.
然后事情变得十分有趣  响起了...
Then things got real interesting. There was a loud...
沉闷的金属声
clunking
像一个...
and a hum like a...
磁铁...一个巨大的磁铁  真的很恐怖
magnet, a big magnet. It was really very frightening.
你知道接下来发生了什么吗?
And do you know what happened next?
没有任何事发生  John
Nothing happened, John.
什么都没发生
Nothing happened at all
你们的计时器
Your timer
又跳回108了
just flipped back to 108.
我从没有输入过数字
I never entered the numbers.
我也从没按过按键
I never pressed the button.
你在说谎
You're lying
不  我没说谎
No, I'm done lying.
Dave
谁是Dave?
Who's Dave?
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
你怎么知道我在哪儿?
How did you know where I was?
Jin在捕鱼的时候看到你了
Jin saw you while he was fishing.
Jin不会说英语
Ha! Jin doesn't speak English.
Sun和他在一起  是她翻译的
Sun was with him. She translated.
Hurley
发生了什么事?
what is going on?
不
No!
你是我恐惧的一部分
You're just the part of me that's scared.
你不想让我醒来
You don't want me to wake up.
你知道么
Well, guess what?
我不怕
I'm not scared.
好的  好的  Hurley...
OK, Hurley,
你有点被恐惧吓倒了
you're having some sort of panic attack.
我了解了
I get that.
但这却不像你
But this isn't like you.
像我?
Like me?
你不了解我
You don't know me.
我正准备了解你
I was starting to.
好的  那你知道我因为胖而杀了两个人么?
Yeah, well, did you know I'm so fat that I killed two people?
知道我还有一个虚构的朋友么?
And that I have an imaginary friend?
Hurley  拜托  你会伤了你自己的
Hurley, please. You're gonna hurt yourself.
不  我不会的
No, I'm not!
因为这不是真的
Because this isn't happening.
全都不是
None of it.
都是我想的  这不是真实的世界
I'm just imagining it. This isn't real life.
你为什么那么说?
Why would you say that?
因为在真实的世界里...
Because in real life...
像你这样的女孩是不会喜欢我的
no girl like you would ever like me.
我记得我说过
You remember when I said
我在哪儿见过你么?
I knew you from somewhere?
也许是因为你是我想出来的
Well, maybe it's 'cause I made you up.
那个断了腿的人叫什么?
What was the man's name who broke his leg?
坠机那天
The day of the crash.
在岛的另一边的那个人?
On the other side of the island,
Eko带了一个断腿的人来找我帮忙
Eko brought a man with a broken leg to me for help.
他叫什么名字?
What was his name?
我...不知道
I don't know.
你不知道  你知道为什么吗?
You don't know. You know why?
因为这是发生在我身上的
Because it happened to me.
他叫Donald
His name was Donald,
是我埋了他
and I buried him.
我埋了很多人  Hurley
I buried a lot of people, Hurley.
所以别告诉我那些都不是真的
So don't tell me that,that wasn't real.
也别告诉我...
And don't tell me
我是你想出来的
you made me up.
那是很无礼的
It's insulting.
今天早上你在海滩看到我的时候...
When you saw me on the beach this morning,
我是拿着一只拖鞋么?
was I holding a slipper?
我记不起来了
No, not that I can remember, no.
Hurley...
看着我
look at me.
我是真的
I am real.
你是真的
You're real.
我对你的感觉...
The way I feel about you,
是真的
that's real
而且这个...
And that...
也是真的
was real.
也许你该再来一次...
Maybe you should do it one more time.
好让我确信
Just to be sure.
可以回去了么?
Ready to go back?
你真的认为我可以...
Do you really think I can,
我是说...改变么?
you know, change?
是的
Yeah.
是的  我确信
Yeah, I do.
你们可以靠近一点
Why don't you get a little closer together?
-说"茄子"  -"茄子"
-Say cheese!  -Cheese!
很好
Great.
你吃药要水么?
You need some water to go with that?
不用  我可以
Nope, I'm good.
那好
OK. Well, fine.
回头见  伙计们  谢谢你们的合作
See you later, guys. Thanks for the photo op.
这是你的药  Libby
Here's your pill, Libby.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====